wallpaperdojo.com 2013-06-08

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

WallpaperDojo takes your privacy seriously and we just hate spam. Please read the following to learn more about how we protect and respect your personal privacy while logged into our web server.

WallpaperDojo has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the following website: wallpaperdojo.com.  
Third party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our web site. These companies may use information about your visits to this web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

Below are links to the privacy policies of the advertising networks used by WallpaperDojo:

* Adsense.com

Third Party Cookies

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.   
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.  
External Links

This site contains links to web sites not owned and not necessarily endorsed by the operators of WallpaperDojo. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external Web sites.

Spam

The operators of this web site do not participate in the practice of spamming. Spamming is the sending of bulk, unsolicited email.

Visitors who submit content to the web site may opt out of having their email address posted on WallpaperDojo's web pages. Additionally, the operators of the site attempt to protect the email addresses of its content providers from email address harvesters by masking or encoding addresses that are reachable through links or forms on the web site.

Contacting WallpaperDojo

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement or the practices of this web site, you can reach the web site operators via email.  
Email: wallpaperdojo@gmail.com
